An Evoluntionary Step
进化的步骤
Saha means with, Ja means born
saha意思是在一起 Ja意思是出生
So it is born with you the right
所以它是你与生俱来的权利
to become united, which is the yoga, with the Divine
成为与上天的联合 那就是瑜伽
We have two sides in our system, of autonomous nervous system, left and right
在我们的系统中分两边 自主神经系统 左边和右边
which we call as left and right sympathetic nervous system
我们称为左右交感神经系统
left side caters for our emotions
左边满足我们情感的需要
for our past, our desires
我们的过去 我们的愿望
the right side caters for our action
右边满足我们行动的需要
physical and mental, if you indulge into one too much
生理和心理 如果你沉迷于一边太多
and go too far with it, you develop imbalance within yourself
走得太远 你的内在发展不平衡
in the center lies the third power which we call as parasympathetic system
在中间存在的第三个力量 我们称为副交感神经系统
This is the channel which is the central path of our ascent
这是我们进化的通道
and the Kundalini rises through it, it brings you in the balance, because it rises in the center of the system
并且昆达里尼沿着这个通道升起 它带给你平衡 因为它沿着系统的中部升起
So this is the minimum that happens that you develop your balance, it is the last breakthrough of our evolution
所以至少要发展你的平衡 这是我们进化的最后突破
Then you have to get connected with the Divine
之后你必须与上天连接
You have to feel it on your central nervous system
你必须在你的中枢神经系统感受到它
And that's how you get your self-realization
那就是你如何获得你的自觉